Register of the Institute of Economic Affairs (Great Britain) records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Walter Allan File, 1987-1993
  - Correspondence, Facsimile messages and letters. Includes enclosures and some correspondence neither to nor from Walter Allan, 1987-1993 (Box 273)
    - Panayiotidis, Andreas, 1991 (Folder 21)
    - Pennant-Rea, Rupert, 1992 (Folder 22)
    - Rivers, Julian, 1991 (Folder 23)
    - Roberts, A. R., 1990 (Folder 24)
    - Rowe, John, Jr., 1991 (Folder 25)
    - Sweet, Darren, 1990 (Folder 26)
  - Itineraries, undated (Folder 27)
  - Memoranda, 1988-1993 (Folder 28)
  - Speeches and writings, 1990-1992
    - Review of Changing Exchange Rate Systems, Typescript, 1990 February 27 (Folder 29)
    - Review of A Biographical Dictionary of Dissenting Economists, Typescript, 1992 February 12 (Folder 30)
  - Subject file, Correspondence, memoranda, printed matter, reports, statistics, and transcripts, largely relating to the activities of the IEA, 1987-1993 (Box 274)
    - Advisory council (Folder 1)
    - Annual general meeting (Folder 2)
    - Audiovisual program (Folder 3-6)
    - Audiovisual program (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Books in store (Folder 2)
    - Catalogue (Folder 3)
    - Conferences and seminars (Folder 4-6)
    - Conferences and seminars (Box 276, Folder 1-2)
    - Development (Folder 3)
    - Education unit (Folder 4)
    - Fellowships (Folder 5-6)
    - Finance (Folder 7)
    - Finance (Box 277, Folder 1-2)
    - Funding and grants (Folder 3)
    - Hayek, Friedrich A. von (Folder 4)
    - Health unit (Folder 5)
    - Housing Choice (Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Russell (Folder 7)
    - Libel insurance (Folder 8)
    - Mailing (Folder 9)
    - Marketing and promotion (Box 278, Folder 1-2)
    - Miller, Robert (Folder 3)
    - Office equipment and services (Folder 4-5)
    - Office equipment and services (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Progress (Folder 2)
    - Publications (Folder 3-4)
    - Reprints and translations (Folder 5)
    - Research Steering Group (Folder 6)
    - Sales representatives (Folder 7)
    - Shadow Monetary Policy Group (Box 280, Folder 1-2)
    - Student internships (Folder 3)
    - Subscriptions (Folder 4)
    - Teachers Resource Centre (Folder 5)
    - Teachers Resource Centre (Box 281, Folder 1-5)
    - Trustees (Folder 6)
    - Universities (Folder 7)
    - Wood, Geoffrey (Folder 8)
- John Burton File, 1968-1989
  Correspondence, research material, and speeches and writings, relating to activities of John Burton, member of the Academic Advisory Council to the Institute.
  - Correspondence (Box 282)
    - The American Spectator, Includes notes, 1983 (Folder 1)
    - Atlas, (Antony Fisher), 1983 (Folder 2)
    - Beacon, G. R., 1977 (Folder 3)
    - Bloomfield, Stephen, 1977 (Folder 4)
    - Body, Richard, 1983 (Folder 5)
    - Flew, Antony, 1981 (Folder 6)
    - Flower, John, 1977 (Folder 7)
    - Foundation National d'Economie Politique (Jean-Jacques Rosa), 1983 (Folder 8)
    - Gillibrand, Maurice, 1989 (Folder 9)
    - Harrigan, Antony (Educational Foundation, United States Industrial Council), 1978 (Folder 10)
    - Heldman, Dan C., 1978-1980 (Folder 11)
    - Institut Economique de Paris (Pascal Salin), 1982 (Folder 12)
    - Joseph, Keith, Sir, 1977 (Folder 13)
    - Peacock, Alan, Includes his typescript on the University College at Buckingham, 1982 (Folder 14)
    - Shavano Institute for National Leadership (John K. Andrews, Jr., George C. Roche, III), 1983 (Folder 15)
    - Three Banks Review (R. G. Baird), 1980 (Folder 16)
    - Vie et sciences economiques (Jean-Francois Hennart), 1980 (Folder 17)
    - Young, Peter (The Centre for Atlantic and European Education (Folder 18)
  - Research material. Includes index cards (Box 283)
    - General. Clippings (Folder 1-2)
    - Australian social contract (Folder 3)
    - Collective bargaining (Folder 4)
    - Competition in policy advice (Folder 5)
    - Competition in the food manufacturing (Folder 6)
    - Direct mailshots (Folder 7)
    - Disputes statistics by country - problems of comparison (Folder 8)
    - Economic and political power of Trade Unions in Britain (Folder 9)
    - Economic Rationale for the use of comparisons in wage bargaining (Folder 10)
    - Economics in industrial subsidies (Folder 11)
    - Effects of employment tax credits (Folder 12)
    - Governmental reputation of industrial relations (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Governments and labour markets (Folder 2)
    - Heritage foundation (Folder 3)
    - Israel (Folder 4)
    - Job regulation and industrial democracy (Folder 5)
    - Labour power in the modern economy (Folder 6)
    - Labour Union and antitrust (Folder 7)
    - Majority rule, exclusive representation, and the interests of individual workers: should exclusivity be abolished? (Folder 8)
    - Markets (Folder 9)
    - Meaning and measurement of partial and disguised unemployment (Folder 10)
    - Membership wage impact of right-to-work laws (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Multinational enterprise (Folder 2)
    - New directions in labour relations (Folder 3)
    - Political economy in greenism (Folder 4)
    - Public duty and union privilege (Folder 5)
    - Public spending (Folder 6)
    - Restriction of output amongst unorganized workers (Folder 7)
    - Right to work (Folder 8)
    - Sponsorship by companies (Folder 9)
    - Thinking and action in industrial relations (Folder 10)
    - Unionism, productivity and growth (Folder 11)
  - Speeches and writings (Box 286)
    - Undated (Folder 1-6)
    - Undated (Box 287, Folder 1-21)
    - Undated (Box 288, Folder 1-7)
    - 1968 (Folder 8)
    - 1976 (Folder 9-10)
    - 1977 (Folder 11-14)
    - 1978 (Box 289, Folder 1-4)
    - 1979 (Folder 5-12)
    - 1980 (Box 290, Folder 1-3)
    - 1981 (Folder 4-7)
    - 1982 (Folder 8-11)
    - 1983 (Folder 12-14)
    - 1986 (Folder 15)
- Antony Fisher File, 1978-1991
  Correspondence, financial records, lists, memoranda, minutes of meetings, programs, proposals, reports, and printed matter, relating to activities of Sir Antony Fisher, co-founder with Oliver Smedley of the Institute.
  - Atlas Economic Research Foundation (Box 291)
    - Cables (Folder 1)
    - Clippings (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, mostly with Ralph Harris, 1978-1983 (Folder 3-5)
    - Financial records (Folder 6)
    - Flyers
      - Election (Folder 7)
      - Recent highlights (Folder 8)
    - Lists
      - Donors, 1982 (Folder 9)
      - International organizations, 1983 (Folder 10)
      - Publications, 1983 (Folder 11)
      - Seminar participants (Folder 12)
      - Tentative social events (Folder 13)
    - Memoranda, 1980-1987 (Folder 14)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1983-1987
      - Board of Directors
        - General (Folder 15)
        - 1983
          - June 23 (Folder 16)
          - August 11 (Folder 17)
          - December 20 (Folder 18)
        - 1984
          - August 27 (Folder 19)
          - Includes agenda for the meeting, November 1 (Folder 20)
        - 1985
          - February 6 (Folder 21)
          - April 8 (Folder 22)
          - August 1 (Folder 23)
          - October 30 (Folder 24)
        - 1986 (Box 292)
          - January 29 (Folder 1)
          - May 14 (Folder 2)
          - May 15 (Folder 3)
          - August 13 (Folder 4)
          - October 1 (Folder 5)
        - 1987
          - January 21 (Folder 6)
          - May 6 (Folder 7)
          - October 27 (Folder 8)
          - December 9 (Folder 9)
      - Trustees of the International Institute for Economic Research
        - 1984 April 25 (Folder 10)
        - 1987 April 14 (Folder 11)
    - Programs, 1983-1987 (Folder 12)
    - Proposal, 1981 (Folder 13)
    - Questionnaire re Atlas Seminar, 1984 (Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1981-1985 (Folder 15)
    - Stationery (Folder 16)
  - Sir Antony Fisher International Memorial Awards, 1990-1991 (Folder 17)
- Ralph Harris File, 1955-1995
  Correspondence, desk calendars, memoranda, notes, reports, research projects, speeches and writings, subject files, and printed matter, relating to activities of Lord Ralph Harris, the Institute's first director, from 1957 to 1987.
  - Biographical file (Box 293)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Draft letter on reasons for resigning from CBI [?] (Folder 2)
    - Letters of congratulation upon Lord Harris's 70th birthday (Folder 3)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - Academics
        - C-D (Folder 4)
        - H-Han (Folder 5)
        - Hao-Hz (Folder 6)
        - I-L (Folder 7)
        - M (Folder 8)
        - N-O (Folder 9)
        - P-R (Folder 10)
        - S-T (Box 294, Folder 1)
        - U-Z (Folder 2)
      - Journalists
        - General
          - Unidentified, arranged in alphabetical order by newspaper affiliation (Folder 3)
          - A (Folder 4)
          - B (Folder 5)
          - C (Folder 6)
          - D-G (Folder 7)
          - H-L (Folder 8)
          - M-Q (Folder 9)
          - R (Box 295, Folder 1)
          - S-U (Folder 2)
          - V-Z (Folder 3)
        - Letters of invitation for journalist/broadcaster lunches (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous organizations
        - A-E (Folder 6)
        - F-Z (Folder 7)
    - Alexander, David, 1968-1973 (Folder 8)
    - Brunner, John, 1965-1975 (Folder 9)
    - Burnet, Alastair (Economist), 1970-1977 (Folder 10)
    - Caine, Sidney, Sir (trustee), 1966-1973 (Folder 11)
    - Centre for Policy Studies (Sir Keith Joseph). See also Subject File/University of the Open Society
      - 1973-1976 (Folder 12)
      - 1977-1983 (Folder 13)
    - Cheaper Food League (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Conservative Research Centre (first Conservative Research Department), 1967-1970 (Folder 2)
    - Dyson, Anthony E., Includes correspondence with C. B. Cox, 1969-1972 (Folder 3)
    - Economics Association
      - 1961-1962 (Folder 4)
      - 1963 (Folder 5)
      - 1964-1980 (Folder 6)
    - Eyres, Stephen (Selsdon Group and Swinton Conservative College), 1969-1977 (Folder 7)
    - Frankel, S. H., 1966-1974 (Folder 8)
    - Freedom Association (first The National Association for Freedom), 1977-1984 (Folder 9)
    - Friedman, Milton
      - 1968-1972 (Folder 10)
      - 1973-1976 (Folder 11)
      - 1977-1979 (Folder 12)
      - 1980-1983 (Folder 13)
    - Institut Economique de Paris, Includes correspondence with Institut de l'Entreprise, 1974-1982 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Institute for the Study of Conflict, 1975-1976 (Folder 2)
    - Ivens, Michael, 1969-1982 (Folder 3)
    - Jewkes, John
      - 1959-1961 (Folder 4)
      - 1962-1963 (Folder 5)
      - 1964-1967 (Folder 6)
      - 1968-1989 (Folder 7)
    - Joseph, Keith (Department of Industry), See also Centre for Policy Studies, 1980 (Folder 8)
    - Lawson, Nigel (Spectator), 1970-1972 (Folder 9)
    - Levin, Bernard, Includes material on Leonid Bukovsky, 1976 (Folder 10)
    - Lynn, Richard
      Includes correspondence on the founding of the Galton Institute of Social Research.
      - 1966-1970 (Folder 11)
      - 1971-1972 (Folder 12)
    - Mason, Douglas, 1968-1973 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Philip, Prince, 1977-1988 (Folder 2)
    - Rose, Harold, 1982 (Folder 3)
    - Saroop, Narindar, 1980-1986 (Folder 4)
    - Shenfield, Arthur A., 1961-1981 (Folder 5)
      Includes three articles by him.
    - Sherman, Alfred, 1969-1987 (Folder 6)
    - Sirc, Ljubo
      Includes undated material in original order.
      - 1960-1964 (Folder 7)
      - 1965-1970 (Folder 8)
      - 1971-1983 (Folder 9)
    - Spearman, Diana, 1965-1978 (Folder 10)
    - Society for Individual Freedom, 1970-1975 (Folder 11)
    - Swinton Conservative College, 1968-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Thorne, Angela (re Ross McWhirter bust) (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - University of St. Andrews, 1970-1971 (Folder 2)
    - Welch, Colin (Daily Telegraph), 1970-1980 (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
  - Day files, 1986
    Consists of correspondence.
    - January-April (Folder 5)
    - May-August (Folder 6)
    - September-December (Folder 7)
  - Desk calendars (Box 300)
    - 1985 (Folder 1)
    - 1986 (Folder 2)
    - 1987 (Folder 3-4)
    - 1988 (Folder 5-7)
    - 1989 (Folder 8)
  - Memoranda, 1972-1987 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Notes (Folder 2)
  - Report, 1971 March 8 (Folder 3)
  - Research projects
    - General
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Agricultural (Folder 5)
      - Draft, Welfare Without the State, 1987 (Folder 6-7)
    - With George Polanyi
      Includes typescripts, notes, correspondence, etc.
      - General
        - General [Polanyi ?] (Folder 8)
        - Biographical note re George Polanyi (Folder 9)
        - Notes on research meetings and programs for further study (Folder 10)
      - After Incomes Policy (Folder 11)
      - Balance of Payments (Folder 12)
      - Capital Investment (Folder 13)
      - Comparative Returns/Capital Return/Return on Capital Investment (Folder 14)
      - Equal Pay (Runnymede Research) (Folder 15)
      - Fuel Policy (abandoned project?) (Box 302, Folder 1)
        Proposals, and correspondence with George Polanyi, David Alexander, and Graham Hutton.
      - Government Expenditure (Folder 2)
      - Housing. See also Subject file/Housing. (Folder 3)
      - Import Controls (Folder 4)
      - Inflation (Folder 5)
      - International Companies (Folder 6)
      - Labour Market (Folder 7)
      - Large Firm Research (Folder 8)
      - Monopolies and Mergers
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Asbestos
          - Runnymede Research (Folder 10)
          - Monopolies Commission Inquiry into the Asbestos Industry (Interim Report, amended November 1971), 1971 April (Folder 11)
        - Detergents (Folder 12)
      - National Lottery (Runnymede Research) (Folder 13)
      - Nationalized Industries (Folder 14)
      - North Sea Gas (Box 303)
        - Undated (Folder 1)
        - 1955-1969 (Folder 2)
        - 1970-1975 (Folder 3)
      - Overseas Investment (Folder 4)
      - Planning, 1967 (Folder 5)
        Includes G. Polanyi's typescript for his book Planning in Britain: The Experience of the 1960's.
      - Poverty. See also Reverse Income Tax. (Folder 6)
      - Redundancy (Folder 7)
      - Resale Price Maintenance
        - Clippings and brochure (Folder 8)
        - Correspondence
          - 1960-1961 June (Folder 9)
          - 1961 July - 1966 (Folder 10)
      - Restrictive Industrial Practices. See also Monopolies. (Folder 11)
      - Reverse (Negative) Income Tax (Box 304)
        - 1967-1968 July (Folder 1)
        - 1968 August-October (Folder 2)
        - 1968 November-December (Folder 3)
        - 1969-1971 (Folder 4)
      - Taxation (Folder 5)
      - Unemployment and Social Benefits (Folder 6)
      - Wealth (Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 8)
  - Speeches and writings
    - General. Statements at the House of Lords
      - Speeches. Cuttings from the official report
        - 1979-1984 (Folder 9)
        - 1985-1989 (Box 305, Folder 1)
        - 1990-1995 (Folder 2)
      - Questions and answers, Cuttings and typescripts, 1980-1984 (Folder 3)
    - "Let's Change the World," See MARTIN WESSELL FILE/Articles collected by Martin Wessell, undated
    - "Principles and Policy," typescript, 1962 October (Folder 4)
    - "Perfect Competition?" letter to the editor, Economist, typescript, 1965 July 20 (Folder 5)
    - "Return to Reality," talk, Third Programme, British Broadcasting Corporation, Typescript, 1968 January 27 (Folder 6)
    - "Morality of Capitalism," talk, St. Lawrence Jewry, typescript, 1974 October 29 (Folder 7)
    - "Like It or not, Our Society Is Based on the Theory of Capitalism," Times, printed copy, 1974 December 4 (Folder 8)
    - "Cheer up! Things Are Getting Worse," Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1975 (Folder 9)
    - "The Economic Problem," Typescript, 1975 January (Folder 10)
    - "Political Victory from the Jaws of Economic Disaster?" [Harris ?]. Typescript, 1975 March 18 (Folder 11)
    - Letter to the editor (with Keith Joseph), Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1975 March 25 (Folder 12)
    - "Case for Dissent," letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1975 May 21 (Folder 13)
    - "Neddy for the Knacker's Yard," Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1975 November 17 (Folder 14)
    - "Inflation, Money and Trade Unions," working paper for Mont Pèlerin Society meeting in Paris, Typescript, 1976 January 15-19 (Folder 15)
    - Article for Reader's Digest, typescript, 1976 January 26 (Folder 16)
    - Statement on the Award of Free Enterprise, typescript, 1976 June (Folder 17)
    - Note on A National Economic Policy, typescript, 1976 June 17 (Folder 18)
    - "Reply for Guests," speech re Bullock Report, typescript, 1977 February 19 (Folder 19)
    - "Foundation of a British Brookings," Times, printed copy, 1977 May 11 (Folder 20)
    - "The Political Economy of Choice in Health and Education," lecture, Marshall Society, Typescript, 1977 July (Folder 21)
    - "Are Trade Unions Really Necessary?" Free Nation, yypescript and printed copy, 1977 July 11 (Folder 22)
    - "Market v. Planning for Future?" preliminary note for CPS Energy Study Group, Typescript, 1977 September 1 (Folder 23)
    - "Tyranny of the Three-Party Welfare State," Daily Telegraph, Typescript and printed copy, 1977 September 22 (Folder 24)
    - "What Would I Do if I Were... a Trade Union Leader," Times, printed copy, 1977 September 23 (Folder 25)
    - "The Positive Way to Project a Free Society," lecture, International Freedom Conference, Oslo, and conclusions of discussion group VI chaired by R. Harris at the conference. Typescripts, 1977 October 11-12 (Folder 26)
    - "New Year Reflections on Forecasting," typescript, 1978 (Folder 27)
    - "What Every Economist Ought to Know," (with Arthur Seldon), Sunday Telegraph, 1978 January 25
      See ARTHUR SELDON FILE/Speeches and writings.
    - "Customer Democracy," typescript, 1978 February (Folder 28)
    - "Come back Adam Smith: All Is Forgiven," Sunday Times, printed copy, 1978 August 20 (Folder 29)
    - "Is the Tide Turning? The British Conundrum," lecture, Mont Pèlerin Society meeting, Hong Kong, Typescript, 1978 September (Folder 30)
    - "Ersatz 'Liberals,'" letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1978 October 28 (Folder 31)
    - "Role of Government Reconsidered," lecture, typescript, 1978 November 24 (Folder 32)
    - "Choice for Euro-Money?" Letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1978 December 11 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - "Cosmos/Micro-Scope/Pol-Econ...," Leader, typescript, 1979 April-May (Folder 2)
    - "State or Market: Have We a Choice?" (with Arthur Seldon), Guardian., 1979 August 6
      Scope and Contents notge
    - "Miners' Ballot?" letter to the editor, Times, typescript, 1984 (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
  - Subject file
    - Adam Smith Club (Folder 5)
    - Bullock Report (Folder 6)
      Includes unidentified manuscript (speech), paper by Arthur Shenfield, and correspondence with John B. Wood. See also Speeches and Writings/Reply for Guests.
    - Copyright, Designs and Patents Bill, 1987-1988 (Folder 7)
    - Galton Institute for Social Research (also Institute for Human Motivation [?]) (Folder 8)
      Includes clippings and correspondence with Nigel Vinson. See also Correspondence/Richard Lynn
    - Housing, 1966-1968 (Folder 9)
      Consists of questionnaires and correspondence (mainly with Mass Observation Limited) re housing survey
    - Institute for Humane Studies (Folder 10)
    - Institute for Analysis of Public Expenditure (proposed) (Folder 11)
    - Longman Sales Statistics (Folder 12)
      Includes correspondence with R. Harris and J. B. Wood.
    - Moon, Sun Myung (sect) (Folder 13)
    - Mont Pèlerin Society, 1968-1986 (Folder 14)
      Includes minutes, aides mémoire, reports, agendas, circulars to directors, and newsletters, all re board meetings.
    - Poleconomy (Box 307, Folder 1-4)
    - Schools Management Training Centre. Proposal for Feasibility Study, Warlingham Park School (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Selsdon Group (Folder 2)
    - Speiser Essay Competition (Folder 3)
    - Student Unions (Folder 4)
    - University of Buckingham (Folder 5)
    - University of the Open Society (Folder 6)
      See also Correspondence/Centre for Policy Studies.
    - Unquoted Companies Group (Folder 7)
  - Subscriber (donor) file ("Prospect files")
    - Fundraising letters
      - A-G (Folder 8)
        Includes letters by G. E. Blundell (treasurer).
      - H-R (Folder 9)
      - S-Z (Folder 10)
    - Subscriber (donor) lists, arranged in chronological order (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Writings by others
    - Unidentified [Harris?], "Whatever Became of Balogh - and Keynes?" Typescript, undated (Folder 2)
    - Butt, Ronald (Times), two articles amended by R. Harris and correspondence, Typescripts, 1975 December - 1976 January (Folder 3)
    - Fisher, Antony G. A. [?], "Can We Be Optimistic?" Daily Express, typescript, 1977 (Folder 4)
    - Jacka, Keith et al., The Rape of Reason, Master typescript, 1975 (Folder 5)
- Graham Mather File, 1987-1993
  Correspondence, memoranda, and printed matter relating to activities of Graham Mather, general director of the IEA until 1992. See also Incremental Materials.
  - Publications file, 1987-1993 (Box 310)
    Correspondence, enclosures, memoranda, and printed matter concerning IEA publications, organized by original file number. Includes some correspondence neither to nor from authors, relating to the topics of IEA publications.
    - Hanson, Charles (08/2/2) (Folder 1-2)
    - Jasay, Antony de (08/2/3) (Folder 3)
    - Bracewell-Milnes, Barry (08/2/4) (Folder 4-5)
    - Bracewell-Milnes, Barry (08/2/4) (Box 311, Folder 1-2)
    - Walters, Alan, Sir (08/2/5) (Folder 3-4)
    - Lithgow, William, Sir (08/2/6) (Folder 5)
    - British Economic Opinion Survey (08/2/7) (Folder 6)
    - British Economic Opinion Survey (08/2/7) (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Economic Affairs (08/2/8) (Folder 2-5)
    - Forthcoming publications, (08/2/9), 1990 (Folder 6)
    - Forthcoming publications, (08/2/10), 1990 (Box 313, Folder 1-2)
    - Forthcoming publications, (08/2/11), 1991 (Folder 3)
    - Forthcoming publications, (08/2/12), 1992 (Folder 4)
    - Tangermann, Stefan (no file number) (Folder 5-6)
  - Subject file, Correspondence, memoranda, and printed matter, relating to the activities of the IEA, 1991-1992 (Box 314)
    - Constitutional reform (Folder 1)
    - Radnitzky, Gerard (Folder 2)
- Keith C. Miles File, 1984-1990
  Correspondence and day files relating to activities of Keith C. Miles, director of finance and operations.
  - Correspondence (Box 315)
    - General
      - 1988 April-December (Folder 1)
        Includes subscriber (i.e. donor) lists of 1986.
      - 1989
        - January-March (Folder 2)
        - April-December (Folder 3)
    - Personal contacts
      - 1984 (Folder 4)
        Includes K. C. Miles' curriculum vitae.
      - 1985 (Folder 5)
      - 1986 (Folder 6)
      - 1987 January-October (Folder 7)
      - 1987 November - 1990 (Box 316)
        - A-G (Folder 1)
        - H-R (Folder 2)
        - S-Z (Folder 3)
          Includes two typescripts by Cento Veljanovski.
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
  - Database printouts listing names of invitees for the Lawson lecture, 1988 June 20 (Folder 5)
  - Day files
    - 1989 October-December (Folder 6)
    - 1990
      - January (Folder 7)
      - February (Box 317, Folder 1)
- John Raybould File, 1982-1990
  Correspondence, forms, invoices, memoranda, minutes, printed matter, and transcripts relating to activities of John Raybould, marketing manager of the Institute.
  - Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 318)
    Facsimile messages and letters. Includes enclosures and some correspondence neither to nor from John Raybould,
    - European Media Support, 1988-1989 (Folder 1)
    - Guild Sound and Vision Ltd.
      - 1986-1988 (Folder 2)
      - 1989 (Folder 3)
      - 1990 (Folder 4)